

Pham Thi Thuy

Android developer

Date of birth: Jun 06, 1998

Gender: Female

Phone: 0373865759

Email: phamthithuyptithcm@gmail.com

Address: Hiep Binh street, Hiep Binh Canh, District 9, HCM

Website: https://github.com/phamthuy1998

OBJECTIVE

I'm a mobile developer with more than one year of experience in mobile development, with knowledge of Object-oriented programming, data structures and algorithms, design patterns. I'm considered a team-player because I like to help others and tend to work well within the group. I love programming and it is very hard to learn new technology.

I would like to work as an android developer in an organization where I can utilize my skills and knowledge related to mobile development and develop robust applications.

EDUCATION

Sep 2016 - Dec 2020 Posts and Telecommunications Institute of Technology

Major: Software development

GPA: 7.95/10 (3.16/4)

Graduation Time: 2021 March.

SKILLS

Programming languages	Java, Kotlin
Tools & Technologies	Kotlin Java:
	+ MVVM architecture
	+ Android Jetpack (Live data, view binding, databinding)
	+ Kotlin Coroutine, thread.
	+ Retrofit/OkHttp
	+ Firebase real-time database, Cloud messaging, FCM, Firebase
	Crashlytics.
	+ Koin, Kodein
	+ Room, Sqlite
	MySql, SQL Server, Bitrise Git, Github, Gitlab
Languages	English: TOEIC 640/990 (IIG Vietnam)
	Vietnamese
Soft Skills:	Teamwork & work independently
	Business communication
	Time management

WORK EXPERIENCE

April 2021 - Present	FPT Software Android Developer
Jun 2020 - March 2021	VINOVA Android Developer Learned: + MVVM architecture + Android Jetpack (Live data, view binding, databinding) + Kotlin Coroutine, thread. + Retrofit/OkHttp + Firebase real-time database, Cloud messaging, FCM, Firebase Crashlytics. + Koin, Kodein + Room, Sqlite
Mar 2020 - May 2020	 VINOVA Android Developer Internship Learn Kotlin, Retrofit, Android Jetpack Learn and apply MVVM architecture to developing weekly projects in progress. Complete Music Player Application for the final project with technical skills such as MVVM, Firebase Auth, Firebase Storage
Jun 2019 - Aug 2019	SWAGSOFT Android Developer Internship Responsibilities: • Learn about Android with Java, managing source with git, clone UI of developing the app of organization.
Sep 2016 - Present	Posts and Telecommunications Institute of Technology Student Clothes App: App selling clothes • Languages: Winform C#, Web API C#, Kotlin, SQL • Technologies: Firebase storage, FCM, MVVM, SQL Server • Github: https://github.com/phamthuy1998/Internship_ClothesManagement Ecommerce app • Language: Kotlin, Java • Technologies: Firebase Storage, Firebase Realtime Database, Firebase Auth, Crashlytics, FCM, MVVM, MVC, Cloud Messaging • Github: https://github.com/phamthuy1998/Ecommerce-App

PROJECTS

VINOVA

(Jun 2020 - Present)

Customer	Delta Gene Flyer
Description	Medical Equipment

Team size	2
My position	Android developer
My responsibilities	Develop new CR Maintenance
Technologies used	+ MVVM architecture + Android Jetpack + Kotlin Coroutine, Thread. + koin + Database with Room, Sqlite query

VINOVA

(Jun 2020 - Present)

Customer	NYP Market Space
Description	Software to support students and staff in MarketSpace.
Team size	10
My position	Android developer
My responsibilities	Develop new CR Maintenance
Technologies used	+ MVVM architecture + Android Jetpack + Kotlin Coroutine, Thread. + Retrofit/OkHttp + FCM. + koin

VINOVA

(Jun 2020 - Present)

Customer	Tackit
Description	App for residents of 5,000 individual estates.
Team size	5
My position	Android developer
My responsibilities	Develop new CR Maintenance
Technologies used	+ Java + MVP architecture + Retrofit/OkHttp